wizardofvegas.com 2019-09-06

# Privacy Policy - Wizard of Vegas

## About the Privacy Policy

The purpose of this policy is to disclose how WizardofVegas.com (WoV) manages the personally identifiable and not otherwise publicly available information collected from its users in accordance with the markets we serve, which includes Europe under the [General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)](https://www.eugdpr.org/). This applies solely to the information gathered during your use (present and past) of the services and products provided by Wizard of Vegas. The policy does not cover the actions of companies not owned or controlled by the [LCB Network](https://lcb.org/network) nor employees outside of our network of sites.

We will refer to WizardofVegas.com as "Website" while the terms "our", "us" and "we" also represent WizardofVegas.com and the LCB Network. Use of the term "you" refers to any individual registered or visiting this Website.

## Collection and Usage of Information

You may be required to provide personal information to us: upon registration, when using our services and products, upon visiting our pages and when entering promotions or sweepstakes.

Your information may be combined with that which we acquire from our business partners or other companies.

The personal information required for registration to this website includes your email address. Optional data you may include in your user profile includes geographical location and gender. You are responsible for keeping these details current.

Our server automatically records information from your browser, such as your IP address, cookie information, and your page request. We will record the IP address of registered members with every posted message/comment on this website for the purposes of geotargeting. We reserved the right to ban your account from this website in the event of abuse and serious violations of this agreement.

We may use your personal information in compliance with your demand for services and products, advertising and customization of the content presented to you, improvement of our services, as a means to contact you, anonymous reporting for internal and external clients, research purposes.

Google Analytics is used to monitor traffic on this website as well as related tools for marketing research and demographics. For more information on how Google Analytics may process your data and how you can opt-out, see [Google's Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy).

Children under the age of 18 are NOT permitted to register at this Website.

## Disclosure and Sharing of Information

Your personal information will not be shared with any 3rd parties unless you've requested a product or service from us or;

  1. We are required to provide the information to the partners who either have a confidentiality agreement with us or work on our behalf. Your personal information may be used by these companies to help us convey offers from us and our marketing partners to you, but they have no right to share this information independently;

  2. In response to court orders, subpoenas and legal processes;

  3. In the event of an investigation, prevention, combating illegal activities, potential threats to the physical safety of any person, suspected fraud, violations of our [Terms and Conditions](https://wizardofvegas.com/terms-conditions/), or as otherwise required by law;

  4. In case of an acquisition or merger, in which case you will be notified before your personal information is transferred and becomes subject to a new privacy policy;

  5. You view or interact with a personal information-based targeted ad, displayed by us, as in that case you are consenting to the possibility that the advertiser may assume that you meet the target criteria used to present the ad. Still, we do not provide any personal information to the advertiser. Advertisers cover a number of industries, including casinos, merchants and travel services.

## Cookies

We may set and access its cookies on your computer. Cookies are information generated by a website and stored on your access device (i.e. computer, smartphone or tablet) by your web browser. We use cookies to recognize your activity and preferences while navigating our site. The majority of browsers automatically accept cookies; however, users may manage cookies in browser settings without compromising the ability to browse the Website. We may also use cookies to identify clicks on affiliate links throughout this website and via promotional emails. Third party cookies are not subject to this privacy policy.

## About Preferences and Editing/Deleting Your Account Info

It is permitted to edit your account details at all times including your communication preferences. Registered members may unsubscribe or amend promotional communication preferences directly from your profile settings or by following â€˜unsubscribe' instructions from email messages you receive. You cannot unsubscribe from receiving certain notifications from us, such as service announcements and administrative messages, as they are a part of your membership. You may request the closure or deactivation of your account at any time. We may also securely delete your personal information per your request.

## Security and Confidentiality Policy

Access to your personal information is limited to our staff members requiring access in order to perform job related duties and/or provide you with services and products. We ensure that your personal information is password protected and safeguarded with physical, electronic, and procedural measures, which are in line with standard laws and regulations. We also use SSL encryption for data transmission protection in certain areas.

## Privacy Policy Updates and Changes

We may make changes to this Privacy Policy. In the event of significant updates directly related to the handling of your personal information, you will be notified via your registered email address and/or a notice displayed on our site.

## Inquiries and Comments

For all inquiries, comments, suggestions, or to request the removal of your information from Website, please contact us [here](https://wizardofvegas.com/contact/).
